<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2019 on 5000164 is here</title><link>https://blog.5000164.jp/2019/</link><description>Recent content in 2019 on 5000164 is here</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 21:28:30 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.5000164.jp/2019/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I went to the meetup which is &#34;Alexey Kotlyarov on Building JSON Codecs with Functional Lenses&#34;</title><link>https://blog.5000164.jp/2019/2/25/meetup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 21:28:30 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.5000164.jp/2019/2/25/meetup/</guid><description>This is the detail about the meetup.
Alexey Kotlyarov on Building JSON Codecs with Functional Lenses | Meetup This was the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve listened to a presentation in English. It was difficult for me. However, if I&amp;rsquo;d listened to the presentation in Japanese, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have understood because I don&amp;rsquo;t know about optics and generic programming. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in optics and generic programming but I haven&amp;rsquo;t studied yet.
I usually use circe when I use JSON, and I, also, sometimes feel bothered. If I had an opportunity to use JSON, I&amp;rsquo;d try to use this method, and I&amp;rsquo;d make the most of the opportunity to study optics and generic programming. It was a good experience for me that I listened to the presentation.</description></item><item><title>SwipePad の代わりに Swiftly Switch を使っている</title><link>https://blog.5000164.jp/2019/2/3/launcher/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 01:03:19 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.5000164.jp/2019/2/3/launcher/</guid><description>SwipePad がなぜか Google Play からなくなっていたので新しいランチャーアプリを探した結果 Swiftly Switch を使っている。 Sidebar, Edge Screen, Shortcuts - Swiftly Switch - Apps on Google Play 他の候補だったアプリは以下。 Smart Task Launcher - Apps on Google Play Swipe Launcher - Apps on Google Play Edge Launcher - Apps on Google Play Pie Control - Apps on Google Play Circle SideBar - Apps on Google Play Swapps! All Apps, Everywhere - Apps on Google Play Meteor Swipe - Edge sidebar launcher - Apps on Google Play Smart One Swipe Launcher - Quick Arc Launcher 2 - Apps on Google Play ssFlicker - Flick &amp;amp; Launch - - Apps on Google Play</description></item></channel></rss>